<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days App</string>
    <string name="app_title">30 Days of 25 Minute Dinner Recipes</string>

    <!-- Food title -->
    <string name = "food_title_01">Creamy Skillet Chicken with Spinach &amp; Mushrooms</string>
    <string name = "food_title_02">Cauliflower Tikka Masala with Chickpeas</string>
    <string name = "food_title_03">Spinach-Artichoke-Sausage Cauliflower Gnocchi</string>
    <string name = "food_title_04">Creamy White Chili with Cream Cheese</string>
    <string name = "food_title_05">This Mushroom-Miso Pasta Is Impossibly Flavorful</string>
    <string name = "food_title_06">Zucchini-Chickpea Veggie Burgers with Tahini-Ranch Sauce</string>
    <string name = "food_title_07">The Easiest Chicken Carbonara (Ready in 20 Minutes!)</string>
    <string name = "food_title_08">Roasted Vegetable &amp; Black Bean Tacos</string>
    <string name = "food_title_09">When You Need Something Quick &amp; Healthy, This 20-Minute Teriyaki Chicken Stir-Fry Has Your Back</string>
    <string name = "food_title_10">Pesto Pasta Salad</string>
    <string name = "food_title_11">White Bean, Kale &amp; Kielbasa Soup Is Ready in Under 20 Minutes</string>
    <string name = "food_title_12">Green Goddess Salad with Chickpeas</string>
    <string name = "food_title_13">Cheese Quesadillas with Peppers &amp; Onions</string>
    <string name = "food_title_14">Spaghetti with Rosemary &amp; Lemon</string>
    <string name = "food_title_15">Chicken Cutlets with Creamy Spinach &amp; Roasted Red Pepper Sauce</string>
    <string name = "food_title_16">One-Skillet Bourbon Chicken</string>
    <string name = "food_title_17">Spinach &amp; Artichoke Dip Pasta</string>
    <string name = "food_title_18">Baked Beans with Ground Beef</string>
    <string name = "food_title_19">Cheeseburger Stuffed Baked Potatoes</string>
    <string name = "food_title_20">Black Bean-Quinoa Bowl</string>
    <string name = "food_title_21">Vegan Coconut Chickpea Curry</string>
    <string name = "food_title_22">Creamy Garlic Skillet Chicken with Spinach</string>
    <string name = "food_title_23">Chicken Fajita Quesadillas Are Packed with 29 Grams of Protein</string>
    <string name = "food_title_24">Lemon-Garlic Pasta with Salmon</string>
    <string name = "food_title_25">Marinara Meat Sauce Topped Baked Potato</string>
    <string name = "food_title_26">Salmon &amp; Avocado Poke Bowl</string>
    <string name = "food_title_27">20-Minute Creamy Chicken Marsala with Prosciutto</string>
    <string name = "food_title_28">Herby Cod with Roasted Tomatoes</string>
    <string name = "food_title_29">Spinach Ravioli with Artichokes &amp; Olives</string>
    <string name = "food_title_30">Lentil Curry with Cauliflower Rice</string>

    <!-- Food Image -->
    <string name = "food_desc_01">Chicken cutlets are topped with a spinach-mushroom cream sauce for a flavorful yet healthy dinner. Serve over pasta or grains to soak up the sauce.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_02">In this vegetarian riff on a popular Indian dish, we swap in cauliflower and chickpeas for the chicken in tikka masala. The cauliflower\'s nooks and crannies are particularly good at soaking up all the intense flavors of the sauce. Serve over rice for an easy healthy dinner that\'s ready in just 20 minutes.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_03">Hearty and piquant, this quick cauliflower gnocchi dinner incorporates several healthy convenience ingredients, including turkey sausage and tender artichoke hearts, so dinner is on your table fast.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_04">This rich, yet healthy, white chicken chili recipe comes together in a flash thanks to quick-cooking chicken thighs and canned white beans. Mashing some of the beans acts as a fast thickener when your soups don\'t have a long time to simmer. Cream cheese adds the final bit of richness and a hint of sweet tang.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_05">This miso pasta features mushrooms, another umami-forward ingredient that takes this quick vegetarian recipe to the next level. We use white miso, which is light and slightly sweet. Whisking the miso into the reserved cooking water makes it easier to incorporate into the pasta.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_06">This veggie burger recipe is one you\'ll want to make again and again. Savory chickpea and zucchini patties are topped with a creamy, herb-flecked tahini ranch sauce, juicy tomato slices and peppery arugula for a satisfying and healthy homemade veggie burger. Serve these vegan burgers on buns or stuff them in pitas. We recommend making extra sauce—it\'s a great dip for veggie sticks and, thinned with a little water, it makes a wonderful salad dressing.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_07">This chicken carbonara has the classic all-yolk sauce, which yields a rich and creamy texture. For some carbonara recipes the residual heat and starch from the pasta are enough to thicken the yolks, but we prefer the double-boiler method to gently cook the egg yolks to a custard-like texture without the risk of overcooking them to a scramble.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_08">These hearty vegan tacos are quick and easy to make, perfect for busy weeknights. They are so tasty no one will miss the meat or dairy.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_09">Look for pre-sliced pepper-and-onion mix in the produce section of the supermarket. It helps save prep time in this quick five-ingredient dinner. This easy dinner calls for hot cooked brown rice, which is perfect if you have leftovers. If not, look for microwaveable brown rice or frozen brown rice to keep prep minimal.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_10">A creamy pesto sauce turns this simple pasta salad into a delightful dinner. Adding broccoli to the pasta cooking water just before the pasta is done is a convenient way to briefly cook it so that it turns a vivid shade of green and softens slightly.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_11">This quick soup recipe is done in only 15 minutes thanks to convenience products like frozen chopped onion and precooked kielbasa. You\'ll have a warming winter soup on the table in no time!</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_12">In this cucumber, tomato, Swiss cheese and chickpea salad recipe, a healthy green goddess dressing is made from avocado, buttermilk and herbs. The extra dressing is delicious served with grilled vegetables.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_13">These 15-minute quesadillas are a notch above basic with the addition of sautéed peppers and onions. Let the kiddos load them up with the toppings at the table.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_14">This recipe, adapted from Eat Better, Feel Better, proves that pasta doesn\'t have to be complicated to be luscious. This dish is very simple but flavorful, so even a smaller portion makes a nice, light meal when paired with a big green salad. You could also add bits of cooked asparagus, broccoli, zucchini—even shrimp if you\'re not going for a meatless main.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_15">Serve these saucy, ultra-quick chicken cutlets over your favorite pasta. This easy dinner recipe is sure to become a new weeknight favorite.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_16">Bourbon chicken gets coated in a slightly sweet-spicy sauce for a flavorful dinner that comes together quickly, making it perfect for busy weeknights.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_17">If you\'ve ever wanted to make a meal out of warm spinach and artichoke dip, this creamy pasta is for you. And here\'s what\'s almost as good as the flavor of this comforting dish: the fact that this healthy dinner takes just 20 minutes to prepare.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_18">Upgrade baked beans from a classic side dish to a meaty main meal by adding lean ground beef. The final result, a hearty casserole, is an easy and fast dinner option.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_19">Skip the bun and serve all of your favorite cheeseburger ingredients—beef, cheese, tomatoes, red onions and lettuce—with baked potatoes for a hearty and easy dinner recipe that kids and adults will love. Feel free to swap out the ground beef for ground turkey or tofu crumbles.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_20">This black bean and quinoa bowl has many of the usual hallmarks of a taco salad, minus the fried bowl. We\'ve loaded it up with pico de gallo, fresh cilantro and avocado plus an easy hummus dressing to drizzle on top.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_21">To make this 20-minute vegan curry even faster, buy precut veggies from the salad bar at the grocery store. To make it a full, satisfying dinner, serve over cooked brown rice. When shopping for simmer sauce, look for one with 400 mg of sodium or less and check the ingredient list for cream or fish sauce if you want to keep this vegan. If you like a spicy kick, add a few dashes of your favorite hot sauce at the end.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_22">Quick-cooking chicken cutlets are coated in a garlic cream sauce, while spinach adds a boost of color and nutrition in this easy, one-skillet recipe.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_23">These 5-ingredient quesadillas take just 10 minutes to make. Using pre-sliced onions and peppers plus a taco seasoning blend helps keep the ingredient list (and prep time) short. If you like a little heat, use pepper Jack cheese in the filling.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_24">Wondering what to do with leftover salmon? This is a delicious and easy way to turn it into another weeknight-friendly, quick dinner. Don\'t forget to reserve some pasta water—its starch thickens the lemon-garlic pasta sauce and makes it silky-smooth.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_25">Break out of your pasta routine by subbing in a baked potato in this simple and satisfying dinner for one.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_26">Poke (pronounced poh-kay), the bite-size marinated fish salad famous in Hawaii, is so popular that it\'s sold by the pound in supermarkets. Now it has crossed the Pacific to become the meal-in-a-bowl du jour, served in eateries from Los Angeles to New York. But it\'s easy to make at home with this quick recipe. Sriracha and Chinese-style mustard add a touch of heat to the classic poke seasoning of soy sauce and sesame oil. Serving it over a brown rice salad makes it a meal.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_27">A bit of prosciutto adds savory flavor to this sauce. Serve this quick-cooking dish with whole-wheat angel hair pasta.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_28">Oregano, thyme and paprika flavor the cod in this 15-minute, Mediterranean-inspired meal. Olives, capers and roasted cherry tomatoes add color and zest to each bite.</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_29">Store-bought spinach ravioli and a handful of basic pantry items are all you need to get a healthy dinner on the table in 15 minutes. Ingredients like oil-packed sun-dried tomatoes, briny Kalamata olives and toasty pine nuts help to build big flavor fast. If you can\'t find frozen artichokes, swap in a 15-ounce can (just be sure to drain and rinse them well).</string>
    <string name = "food_desc_30">Combine precooked lentils (often located in the produce section of your grocery store) with an Indian-style simmer sauce for a super-fast and flavorful curry. Serving it over riced cauliflower bumps up the vegetable count and keeps carb servings in check. This 3-ingredient dinner (not counting salt, pepper and oil) is really as easy as it gets. To be mindful of the salt, look for simmer sauces with less than or close to 350 mg sodium per ¼-cup serving.</string>
</resources>